Doctor.
طبيب.
If you are free,
إذا كنت متفرغاً،
you can make some tonic soup
يمكنك تحضير بعض حساء التونيك
to bring here for the patient.
لإحضارها إلى هنا من أجل المريض.
Mengmeng.
منغمينغ.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
The doctor said
قال الطبيب
you finally woke up.
لقد استيقظت أخيراً.
Do you know how worried I've been
هل تعلم كم كنت قلقاً؟
about you during this time?
ماذا عنك خلال هذه الفترة؟
Wenjie,
وينجي،
don't cry.
لا تبكي.
Lu Xing's vital signs are all normal now.
أصبحت جميع العلامات الحيوية للو شينغ طبيعية الآن.
What you should do now
ما يجب عليك فعله الآن
is to take care of yourself.
أن تعتني بنفسك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Do you feel uncomfortable anywhere?
هل تشعر بعدم الارتياح في أي مكان؟
Do you have a headache?
هل تعاني من صداع؟
Or anywhere else?
أو في أي مكان آخر؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
Xing wants you inside.
يريد شينغ أن تدخل.
you look
أنت تبدو
different from before.
مختلف عن السابق.
How so?
كيف ذلك؟
You look
أنت تبدو
like a rich lady now.
مثل سيدة ثرية الآن.
I'm a big boss
أنا رئيس كبير
with
مع
a fortune of billions now.
ثروة تُقدر بمليارات الدولارات الآن.
Blue Crane has won
فاز فريق بلو كرين
has been taken over by Blue Crane.
تم الاستحواذ عليها من قبل شركة بلو كرين.
Once the process is completed,
بمجرد اكتمال العملية،
we'll hold a groundbreaking ceremony.
سنقيم حفل وضع حجر الأساس.
Once the project is operational,
بمجرد أن يصبح المشروع جاهزاً للتشغيل،
it can bring in
يمكنه أن يجلب
over a billion yuan in revenue annually.
إيرادات سنوية تتجاوز مليار يوان.
How about it?
ما رأيك؟
Do you want to
هل تريد أن
come work for me?
هل ترغب بالعمل معي؟
I'll pass.
سوف أمر
I'm still
ما زلت
just a nobody.
مجرد شخص عادي.
Come on.
تعال.
You could have restored your identity long ago.
كان بإمكانك استعادة هويتك منذ زمن بعيد.
It's just to stay by Wenjie's side
كل ما في الأمر هو البقاء بجانب وينجي
in a legitimate way.
بطريقة مشروعة.
Right.
يمين.
You are much braver than before.
أنت الآن أكثر شجاعة من ذي قبل.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Mengmeng.
منغمينغ.
You should be braver.
يجب أن تكون أكثر شجاعة.
Let bygones
دع الماضي يمضي
be bygones.
لنطوي صفحة الماضي.
Vivi and I
أنا وفيفي
hope you can live a happy life.
أتمنى لك حياة سعيدة.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Why did you buy a cake?
لماذا اشتريت كعكة؟
I just saw it.
لقد رأيته للتو.
It's not bad.
ليس سيئاً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You gave me a full set.
لقد أعطيتني مجموعة كاملة.
Don't waste it.
لا تضيعه.
Make a wish.
تمنى أمنية.
[It turns out that]
[اتضح أن]
[he has already celebrated my birthday.]
[لقد احتفل بالفعل بعيد ميلادي.]
What are you thinking about?
بماذا تفكر؟
Are you thinking about Qing?
هل تفكر في سلالة تشينغ؟
Who's thinking about him?
من يفكر فيه؟
This is our company's team building.
هذا برنامج بناء الفريق الخاص بشركتنا.
What does it have to do with him?
ما علاقة ذلك به؟
He's been too busy lately.
لقد كان مشغولاً للغاية في الآونة الأخيرة.
He probably won't come today.
من المحتمل أنه لن يأتي اليوم.
He asked me to take care of you.
طلب مني أن أعتني بك.
How about playing cards together?
ما رأيكما في لعب الورق معاً؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Come on.
تعال.
Mr. Xu, come and play cards with me.
سيد شو، تعال والعب معي الورق.
Mr. Xu, come on.
السيد شو، هيا.
Come on.
تعال.
Deal the cards.
وزّع الأوراق.
He asked me to take care of you.
طلب مني أن أعتني بك.
Let me get you some more
دعني أحضر لك المزيد
chips.
رقائق البطاطس.
Joker.
مهرج.
I want it.
أريدها.
Four Js.
أربعة جاءات.
Why don't you ask me
لماذا لا تسألني؟
why Qing is so busy?
لماذا تشينغ مشغول للغاية؟
Why?
لماذا؟
He's busy for you.
إنه مشغول من أجلك.
I didn't expect he would do this.
لم أتوقع أن يفعل هذا.
For me?
لي؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
He started
بدأ
an orphan charity foundation for you.
مؤسسة خيرية للأيتام من أجلك.
He spent money
أنفق المال
and effort on it.
وبذل الجهد في ذلك.
I didn't ask him to do this.
لم أطلب منه أن يفعل هذا.
What money? What effort?
أي مال؟ أي جهد؟
Women are so heartless.
النساء قاسيات القلب للغاية.
Wang.
وانغ.
Da Wang.
دا وانغ.
One left.
بقي واحد.
Four zeros.
أربعة أصفار.
This looks so delicious.
هذا يبدو شهياً للغاية.
Am I late?
هل تأخرت؟
To apologize,
للاعتذار،
I bought cakes for everyone.
اشتريت كعكات للجميع.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
شكراً لك يا سيد لين.
You came just in time.
لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب تماماً.
The food is ready.
الطعام جاهز.
Let's dig in.
هيا بنا نبدأ.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll toast to everyone.
سأرفع نخبًا للجميع.
This project
هذا المشروع
is successful
ناجح
because of everyone's hard work.
بفضل العمل الجاد للجميع.
Thank you all.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
Tomorrow is a holiday.
غداً عطلة رسمية.
You can do whatever you want.
يمكنك أن تفعل ما تشاء.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
شكراً لك يا سيد شو.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Well done!
أحسنت!
Thank you, boss!
شكراً لك يا رئيس!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Let's dig in!
هيا بنا نبدأ!
Have more broccoli, it's tasty!
تناول المزيد من البروكلي، إنه لذيذ!
The broccoli is really good!
البروكلي لذيذ جداً!
Have more!
احصل على المزيد!
I actually think this is quite nice.
أعتقد في الواقع أن هذا جميل جداً.
Don't you think?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
can I add you on WeChat?
هل يمكنني إضافتك على تطبيق وي تشات؟
152643...
152643...
1532.
1532.
Why are you giving out my number again?
لماذا تعطي رقمي مرة أخرى؟
I'll add you then.
سأضيفك إذن.
Remember to accept.
تذكر أن تقبل.
Come and play together.
هيا نلعب معاً.
Let's play the King game.
هيا نلعب لعبة الملك.
The person who draws the King card
الشخص الذي يسحب بطاقة الملك
can order anyone
يمكن لأي شخص أن يطلب.
who draws another card
من يسحب بطاقة أخرى
to do anything.
أن يفعل أي شيء.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Understood.
مفهوم.
Got it.
فهمتها.
This one is good.
هذا جيد.
I'll take this one.
سآخذ هذا.
I want this one.
أريد هذا.
Who is the king?
من هو الملك؟
Who is?
من هو؟
I am the king.
أنا الملك.
Mr. Xu, pick someone.
سيد شو، اختر شخصاً.
Then,
ثم،
No. 3 and No. 7,
رقم 3 ورقم 7،
have a drink.
تناول مشروب.
Who is No. 7?
من هو رقم 7؟
I'm No. 7.
أنا رقم 7.
Then you two...
ثم أنتما الاثنان...
It's you. Drink up.
أنت هو. اشرب.
Again.
مرة أخرى.
You guys are playing too conservatively.
أنتم تلعبون بأسلوب متحفظ للغاية.
If I drew the King card...
لو سحبت ورقة الملك...
Draw a card.
اسحب بطاقة.
Come on.
تعال.
Choose quickly.
اختر بسرعة.
I am the king.
أنا الملك.
Who should I choose?
من عليّ أن أختار؟
Then...
ثم...
Number five.
رقم خمسة.
Who are you choosing? Choose quickly.
من تختار؟ اختر بسرعة.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Number five.
رقم خمسة.
Another one.
واحد آخر.
Who should I choose?
من عليّ أن أختار؟
Oh, come on, I'm dying of impatience.
يا إلهي، أنا أموت من نفاد الصبر.
Which number should I choose?
أي رقم يجب أن أختار؟
Number six then.
إذن، الرقم ستة.
Who is number six?
من هو صاحب الرقم ستة؟
Number five and number six
الرقم خمسة والرقم ستة
eat a biscuit together.
تناولوا البسكويت معاً.
The two of them keep biting.
يستمر الاثنان في العض.
Bite.
يعض.
Bite to the middle.
قضم من المنتصف.
It must not exceed one centimeter.
يجب ألا يتجاوز سنتيمترًا واحدًا.
This is doable.
هذا ممكن.
Who is No. 5?
من هو رقم 5؟
Not me.
ليس أنا.
Me.
أنا.
Who is No. 6?
من هو رقم 6؟